[{"answer": "Well, it's the $64,000 question.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Why do you think nothing happened?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm so thankful that these survivors came forward because maybe we can put an end to the notion that, A, boys don't get sexually abused, or the fact that we can't get enough evidence to get what I think is frankly a monster who has groomed, who used his power of authority to take advantage of these victims -- survivors and survivors and their families.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What is your assessment of what's been going on this week in court?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "This is going to sound strange but I think the best gift the prosecution has is that they can't put on expert testimony.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "And what difference does that make to a jury's ability to comprehend perhaps some of what is going on and what they're hearing?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, when you have been abused the way they were abused, not just abused physically but also emotionally, and abuse of trust, every trauma can be a layer.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "And how traumatic is it to come to a courtroom and relive the abuse that maybe in some cases they've hidden from family and friends?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Let me tell you, Piers, I don't think there's a child out there who hasn't been sexually abused and isn't right now reliving what these young men are, in fact, testifying, too, and how they're having to relive it as I talk to you tonight.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What do you think these boys who are now men have been going through to have to relive in public what they went through?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "No, I think -- I think she knew.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Do you think it's conceivable that Dottie Sandusky, Jerry's wife, knew nothing about any of this?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, I know, you know, having -- before I went to Save the Children, I started a program for juvenile delinquency kids in Baltimore.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "What do you think of the whole Sandusky case?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "You know, after he died, I essentially didn't know what to do.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What was the purpose?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Did he really?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I think, you know, political debates, campaigns are tough.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What would he have made of that?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, I thought their contrasting speeches today were very revealing.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What do you think is now the dividing line between Governor Romney and President Obama?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's laid out a very specific plan with respect to tax policy.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Is it completely off the table that he would do that?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, one of the unfulfilled promises of the Obama presidency is his explicit pledge to change Washington and to reduce the partisanship there.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Are you sensitive to that, that charge that actually the drive to push out Barack Obama from the Republican side and Governor Romney's side, that actually the national interest can get damaged here, and that there is a need up to the election for the business of running America to be allowed to continue?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, I think what I would say is we're cognizant of the fact -- well, I don't know if I can say it in one word.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Are you feeling increasingly confident in the Romney camp?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, what I was going to say, if I were able to finish what I was about to say, was that the president has continuously said, well, we've made progress.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "So you've definitely hit a bit of a wall at a very difficult time for you with the campaign, haven't you?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, it's not about whether we need to grow our economy.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What are the admissions that you're prepared to make to the American public as we head towards the election?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I think that if you look at what Clinton said, Piers, he said there's two different ways that you can conduct business.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "So how did you guys feel when President Clinton comes out and says the complete opposite?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Neither.", "docId": "120614pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Finally, give me a word answer tot his, do you feel more comfort now winning the election than you did, say, a month ago or less confident?", "qSentId": 533}]